igomyway.com 2017-01-18

# 

**_Purpose_**

This Privacy Policy (hereinafter: the “ **Policy** ”) governs the terms and conditions on how the user’s (hereinafter: “ **User** ” or “ **you** ”) personal or anonymous information is collected, stored during the visit to or use of the website [www.igonavigation.com](http://www.igonavigation.com/) operated by NNG Software Developing and Commercial LLC (registered seat: H-1037 Budapest, Szépvölgyi út 35-37, Hungary; hereinafter: “ **NNG** ” or the “ **Company** ”). This Policy informs you of all aspects of how your personal data is processed, such as the purpose for which your data is required and the legal basis thereof, the types of data subject to processing, the duration of the proposed processing operation, and your rights and remedies. Please read this Policy carefully!

Please note that the site contains links to third-party websites. The use of a third-party website is not subject to this Policy, it is governed by the terms of its own privacy policy. Once you click on any of the external links or relevant button, NNG will no longer have any influence over the collection, storage, or processing of any personal data transmitted to the third-party website.

To use certain function on the website, the User shall provide their personal data specified in this Policy, and NNG may collect the User’s personal data specified below during the User’s visit to or use of the website. The majority of the information on the website is accessible without the provisions of your personal data; however, the contact function is only available if you provide the requested personal data. It is a condition of the use of the website that the visitor or the User using the functions available on the website accept the terms and conditions of this Policy.

During the operation of the website and the provision of certain services available on the website, NNG shall comply with the effective legislation on data processing, in particular with the provisions of Act CXII of 2011 on the Right of Informational Self-Determination and on Freedom of Information (hereinafter: the “ **Privacy Act** ”) and the recommendations made by the National Authority For Data Protection And Freedom Of Information. NNG shall comply with the relevant European Union legislation if it is directly applicable.

 ** _Data Controller_**

The data provided on the website is controlled by **NNG Software Developing and Commercial LLC** (registered seat: H-1037 Budapest, Szépvölgyi út 35-37, Hungary; hereinafter: “ **NNG** ” or the “ **Company** ”). The provided data is accessible to NNG’s employees and managers involved in the accomplishment of the purpose of the data processing, and IT specialists performing a variety of IT tasks related to the operation and maintenance of NNG’s computer system.

###  ** _Legal Basis of Data Processing_**

The legal basis of data processing is the authorization conferred by law, or the User’s _consent_ pursuant to point a) of Section 5(1) of the Privacy Act, that is, the data processing is voluntary. However, in certain cases, if the consent is withdrawn, point b) of Section 6(5) of the Privacy Act may also serve as a legal basis of data processing, if the relevant legal requirements are met.

By using the website and by providing the data, you expressly and voluntarily give your consent that NNG controls your personal data in accordance with the provisions under this Policy and the effective legislation on privacy. By providing your personal contact information and accepting this Policy, you acknowledge that you have understood and accepted the provisions of this Policy, and give your express consent to NNG to control your personal data in compliance with the terms and for the purposes set forth in this Policy.

###  ** _Data Security_**

NNG observes the regulations regarding the security of personal data and implements adequate safeguards and appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect personal data, as well as adequate procedural rules to enforce the provisions of the Privacy Act and other regulations on confidentiality and data security. In particular, NNG implements appropriate measures to protect personal data against unauthorized access, alteration, transmission, public disclosure, deletion, or destruction, including measures designed to provide access to the databases containing personal data exclusively by employees who are involved in the accomplishment of the purpose of the data processing, or need access in order to perform their tasks of troubleshooting. In the event of a data incident, NNG shall meet its obligation of notification as set forth in the effective legislation, and shall immediately meet its procedural obligation to cease the infringement of law.

 ** _Information about Website Visits_**

Please be informed that by downloading certain parts of the website, your device will automatically receive small data files (“cookies”) sent by the web server. In certain cases, these data files may be considered as personal data under the Hungarian law on privacy. These data files are used to provide the satisfactory operation of the website and collect anonymous information on website visits. You can control the use of cookies by setting your browser accordingly, however, if you choose to disable the cookies it may result that some website features or services will not work properly.

Applied cookie: Google Analytics

Purpose: The website uses Google Analytics to analyze visits to the website and collect information on how and where the Users use the website. NNG uses this information to produce reports and improve the website. The collected data is anonymous, including the number of Users to the website and the information on where the Users come to the website from and which pages they visit. The collected data is non-identifying and cannot be associated with the given User. For further information on Google’s privacy policy, [_click here_](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies/).

Applied cookie: Session

Purpose: Session cookies allow the Users to be recognized while visiting the website. The information is saved until the end of the session, after which the collected information is longer available.

Applied cookie: Persistent

Purpose: Persistent cookies remember the language settings applied by the User. The cookies are automatically deleted after a period of 1 year.

On the various access levels of the website, NNG’s servers automatically record (log) the User’s IP address, type of browser and operation system, URL of the visited pages, and time of page views. The data controlled by NNG is aggregate, automated, and processed, and is used to correct errors detected on the website, and for QA and statistical purposes.

 ** _Information on the Use of the Contact Function Offered on the Website_**

Your personal data is processed if you provide the following personal information to contact NNG through the website:

  * Full name
  * Email address
  * Country
  * Product name
  * Personal data provided in the message

You cannot contact NNG without providing the above data. In terms of data protection, “ _personal data_ ” shall mean data relating to the natural person (data subject), in particular by reference to the name and identification number of the data subject or one or more factors specific to their physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity as well as conclusions drawn from the data in regard to the data subject. The User represents that all personal data provided by the User on the website is correct and accurate.

 ** _Purpose of Data Processing_**

NNG shall process the personal data exclusively in accordance with the information provided for the User, for achieving a pre-defined, well-specified purpose. NNG only processes personal data that is essential for the purpose for which it was collected, and that is suitable for achieving that purpose. The personal data may be processed to the extent and for the duration necessary to achieve said purpose.

The purpose of contact data processing is to answer the question or respond to the request communicated to NNG, examine the issue, inform the User about NNG’s reply, monitor the quality of the customer care service, measure efficiency, and prepare statistics.

 ** _Duration of Data Processing_**

The data provided by the User for contact purposes shall be controlled by NNG as long as the purpose of data processing is achieved, and shall be deleted upon the achievement of the purpose or in failure thereof, after 2 years after the registration of the data.

###  ** _Rights and Remedies_**

Upon request, your data will be deleted at any time. Request for data deletion may be submitted to NNG by writing to the electronic or postal address specified below. NNG will also delete all personal data which is no longer necessary for the accomplishment of the purpose, or if the storage of the personal data is legally inadmissible. Personal data, the processing of which is subject to legal obligation, will not be affected.

You may request information on your personal data being processed—in particular the purpose, legal basis, or duration of processing, the legal basis and addressee of the data transmission, the conditions and effects of data incidents—by writing to [customersupport@igonavigation.com](mailto:customersupport@igonavigation.com) or H-1037 Budapest, Szépvölgyi út 35-37, Hungary. NNG shall provide the requested information in writing without any delay, within not more than 25 days. The information shall be provided free of charge for any category of data once a year. Additional information concerning the same category of data may be subject to a charge. Where any payment is made in connection with data that was processed unlawfully, or the request led to rectification, it shall be refunded.

You may request the rectification or blocking of your personal data as described above. Where your personal data is deemed inaccurate, and the correct personal data is at NNG’s disposal, NNG shall rectify the personal data in question.

The personal data shall be erased if processed unlawfully; so requested by the User; is incomplete or inaccurate and cannot be lawfully rectified, provided that the erasure is not disallowed by a statutory provision of an act; the purpose of processing no longer exists or the legal time limit for storage has expired; so ordered by court or by the Authority. The personal data shall be blocked instead of being erased if so requested by the data subject, or if there are reasonable grounds to believe that the erasure could affect the legitimate interests of the data subject. The blocked data shall be processed only for the purpose which prevented its erasure.

In the event any data is rectified, blocked, marked, or erased, the data subject and all recipients to whom it was transmitted for processing shall be notified. Please be informed that your data may not be erased if the processing thereof is prescribed by law.

You may use either of the above contact addresses to object to the processing of data relating to you

\- if the processing (transmission) is carried out solely for the purpose of discharging the controller’s legal obligation or for enforcing the rights and legitimate interests of the controller, the recipient, or a third party, unless the processing is prescribed by law;

\- if the personal data is used or transmitted for the purposes of direct marketing, public opinion polling, or scientific research;

\- if the enforcement of your right to object is otherwise granted by the effective laws.

In the event of objection, NNG shall investigate the cause of objection within the shortest possible time but not more than 15 days, adopt a decision as to its merits, and shall notify the data subject of its decision in writing. If, according to NNG’s findings, the data subject’s objection is justified, NNG shall terminate all processing operations (including data collection and transmission), block the data, and notify all recipients to whom any of these data has been transmitted of the objection and the ensuing measures, upon which the recipients shall also take measures to enforce the data subject’s right of objection.

If the User disagrees with NNG’s decision on the User’s objection, or if the User’s rights are violated, or if NNG fails to meet the above specified deadline, the User may turn to court within 30 days after the date of receipt of the decision or the last day of the time limit. The action shall be heard by the competent tribunal. Upon your request, pursuant to the effective legislation, the action may be brought before the tribunal in whose jurisdiction your home address or temporary residence is located.

You may lodge a complaint about the processing of your personal data to the National Authority for Data Protection and Freedom of Information (address: H-1125 Budapest, Szilágyi Erzsébet fasor 22/C.; postal address: H-1530 Budapest, Pf. 5.; phone: +36-1-391-1400; fax: +36-1-391-1410; email: [ugyfelszolgalat@naih.hu](mailto:ugyfelszolgalat@naih.hu); www.naih.hu) , or turn to court as provided for in the Privacy Act. Your rights and remedies are governed by Sections 14–18 and 21–23 of the Privacy Act.

This Policy was published on 18.04.2016 and is effective as of that date.
